AHMAD FAHRUDIN

Web Developer

Phone +62822 2565 6828 Email : ahmadrockets@gmail.com Website : https://ahmadrockets.github.io

Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/ahmad-fahrudin

Profile

Web developer with more than 6 years of experience in developing, crafting, and programming website or web applications. Have experience in developing small to large web applications. Able to work with teams, and complete projects efficiently. Also actively learn new technology to grow.

Skills

PHP, MySQL, PostgreeSQL, Golang, Codeigniter, Yii, Laravel, MVC, Javascript, jQuery, Ajax, VueJS, React JS, JSON, APIs, Rest, HTML 5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Node JS, Linux.

Experience

Web Developer

April 2021 - October 2021 (Contract)

Logique Digital Indonesia

Developing software using (Laravel, Node JS, Vue JS, Cakephp). Collaborate with QA, and team. Fixing any bug, use gitlab.

Frontend Web Developer

January 2021 - April 2021

PT. Infosys Solusi Terpadu

Developing software using (React JS, Redux, responsive design), collaborate with backend and QA Team, slicing figma to UI, using gitlab.

Full Stack Web Developer

September 2014 - November 2020

CV. Diginet Media

- Designing, coding and developing E-Government software.
- Designing database MySQL, PostgreeSQL.
- Backend coding with Native PHP, Laravel, Codeigniter, and Yii.
- Frontend with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery, Ajax.
- Collaboration with QA.
- Troubleshooting any bug.
- Use GitLab.

Education

Universitas PGRI Yogyakarta

2016 - Present

Bachelor's Degree, Information Technology

SMK N 2 WONOSARI (Vocational High School)

2011 - 2014

Computer and Network Engineering

Portofolio

Aplikasi Tanya Jawab Seputar Koding (Like Stackoverflow)

Url: https://dry-woodland-06720.herokuapp.com/ Github: https://github.com/indrarasyid07/finalproject

Colaborate with friends designing web applications such as stackoverflow which serve to post questions or answer questions. There is a feature to rate questions or answers. Using PHP Laravel, MySQL, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, Javascript, ¡Query, Ajax.

Phone Review Golang API

Url: https://phone-app-golang.herokuapp.com/swagger/index.html

Github: https://github.com/ahmadrockets/review-phone-golang

Simple API for phone review, using Golang, Gin, Gorm, and swagger for documantation

api with MySQL / PostgreeSQL for database. .

Simple React Lyric Finder with Musixmatch API

Url: https://carilirik.netlify.app/

Github: https://github.com/ahmadrockets/react-simple-lyric-finder

Simple web apps which provides a search facility for song lyrics and artists, which is integrated with musixmatch api. Using React JS, Bootstrap, Axios, and integrated with Musixmatch API.

Simple Vue Todo List

Url: https://vuetodofah.netlify.app/

Github: https://github.com/ahmadrockets/vue-simple-todo

Simple web apps todo that can add or delete todo list. This web apps using Vue JS, Vuex,

and Tailwind CSS.